Hi and welcome. My name is Defanaric and I will be your instructor for this course.
I'm delighted to have you here. I really hope that you will enjoy this course
and that you will go all the way through with it. So this is just a two-minute
introduction so that you get to know me and then we'll hop right into the course.
I'm French so if you hear a small accent this is where it comes from. It's the
sweet country of France. But I've also lived in the United States in Australia and
now in Portugal. My expertise is going to be around AWS
certifications and Apache Kafka. Why? Well because in my career I've had the
chance to be a data analyst, a big data engineer, a developer and a solutions
architect. Well obviously nowadays I'm a teacher. I love to teach and this is my
passion and I'm going to help you achieve any goals you have through online learning.
So before you get started with this course there are two ways you can connect with me.
The first place is on LinkedIn. So this is where I will share some news about
AWS and the Kafka ecosystem. This is where I announce new courses
and this is where I congratulate my students. So for example if you've
completed the course or you passed a certification make a post on LinkedIn
and tag me and I will make sure to congratulate you. I love to see my students
raise your goals. This is my main motivation. The second way is on Instagram.
So Instagram is a big part of mine that I've started several years ago.
So I love to travel the world and I dedicate some of my time
to actually meet my students and to date I've already met over 40 students.
So every time I meet students we'll have a chat about your goals, about how
the course helped you in your career and just general shot about life
and at the end of it I will make a post on Instagram. So if you want to get the
chance to meet me or to read about other student stories then follow me on
Instagram. Finally before starting this course I want you to set a goal.
By setting a goal you will have a much higher chance of finishing this course
and learning a lot. So maybe you want to finish this course in three weeks
that's perfect. This is how you learn and this is how you will make the most out of
this course. And don't hesitate to go through the videos as many times as needed.
This is what videos are used for. If necessary you can speed up the video
or slow it down so it becomes easier for you to understand me.
So that's it for me. I hope you will enjoy the course
and I will see you in the next lecture. Happy learning!